http://www.sprinkler.com/policy.php#E

Controllers - Timers
Cabinets PedestalsDecodersIndoorModulesOutdoorPanels transformers etcPanels, Transformers, Etc.Pump start relaysSensorsbattery operated
Drainage
Drain Pipe ConnectorsDrainage Pipe
Drip Irrigation
AdaptersDrip Zone kits, Valces, root wateringEmitters NozzlesFilters, Pressure reducersFittingsStakes, heads
Irrigation Filters
ActionAmiadRainbird
Irrigation Supply
ConduitFlangesFunny pipeHoseHose FittingsMetal FittingsPVC Flex PipePVC PipePipe AccessoriesPipe GluePoly ethyleneMore Irrigation Supply...
Irrigation Tools
Drip ToolsPipe Tools
Irrigation Valves
BallBrassBronzeCheckElectricGateManifoldsManualPVCQuick CouplingStop and wastesMore Irrigation Valves...
Help & Feedback
Live in Utah?
Latest Products
Action Machining 18011-1.5 1.5" MIPT x Buttress Transition Nipple
$6.99
Action Machining 18011-.750 3/4 x 1 inch Buttress Transition Nipple
$1.99
Action Machining 18010-2.0 2" Manifold Male Adapter
$10.42
Action Machining 18010-.750 3/4 MIPT x 1 inch Female Buttress Nut
Price Match Guarantee
Sprinkler.com is committed to providing our customers with the best online price. If you find a lower price on any identical, available product and meet the terms and conditions we will match it guaranteed!
Shipping & Delivery
Our fulfillment team works hard to get your order out as quickly as possible. Most orders ship within 1-2 business days. Please note that backordered items may take 1-2 weeks before they are shipped. We try to be as accommodating and flexible as possible, so if you have a concern about when your item will ship please call us to make special arrangements. We ship most orders FedEx Ground, but expedited options are available. All shipments are fully trackable and ship FedEx wherever possible.
Tax Policy
We are required to collect tax on all orders billing to Utah. The cost will automatically be updated during checkout.
Privacy & Security
Sprinkler.com respects your privacy. We do not sell or transfer any personal information to anybody. Personal information is only required for the purchasing of materials from our online store. All other personal information is optional and is willfully sent by the user.
Information containing no personally identifiable data will be used by us and certain contracted third parties. Such information includes, but is not limited to, use of cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics on our web site visitors. Information is used for reporting web traffic, statistics, advertisement click-throughs, and/or other activities on our site. This data helps us improve the quality of our site and make it more user friendly to visitors. No personal information or personally identifiable data is collected by or transmitted to third parties at any time.
Accounts:
Sprinkler.com account information is for personal use only. By using such service you agree to keep viewable information confidential and to not disclose pricing, availability, and/or other data to anyone other than those within the accounts organization. We have the right to discontinue said service to any person or organization at any time.
If you have questions about our Privacy Policy please contact us.
Returns
At Sprinkler.com we are committed to your satisfaction. We stock quality lawn sprinkler and irrigation parts to ensure that satisfaction. Sprinkler.com will accept product returns on the following:
Satisfaction Guaranteed:
Product will be received back into inventory without a restocking fee if you are not satisfied with your order. Please send an email, to customersupport@sprinkler.com, requesting a Return Authorization within 30 days of the date product is received.
All Other Returns:
If for any other reason you need to return an item you may do so within 30 days of the date the product was received. Before product is returned, please obtain a Returns Authorization Number so we know what needs to be done with the returned package. Product returned must be in new condition. Returns are subject to a 15% restocking fee. Customer will be credited the price of item(s) at purchase minus any discounts on the order. Customer is responsible for shipment and charges to get product back to our Sandy, Utah location. Clearance items, special order items, and cut wire/pipe are not returnable.
Warranty
Product warranties are provided by the manufacturer of the product. Please review the full warranty information within the manufacturer packaging. For more information on your product's warranty, please visit the manufacturer's website, or contact them directly.
